瑞秋,履历表已用完了
We're running low on resumes.
你真想到“大众技工”上班吗?
You want a job with Popular Mechanics?
如果你真想为技工工作 那儿倒儿可试试
If you're gonna work for mechanics,those are the ones.
各位,我什么都得试试 我不能再当服务生了
Guys,I'm going for anything here. I can't be a waitress anymore.
我是说真的我已厌倦微薄小费 我已厌倦别人对我说“麻烦一下”
I'm sick of the lousy tips. I'm sick of being called "Excuse Me."
-伤到舌头了!伤到舌头了! -这里
-Paper cut! Paper cut! -Here.
柚子汁!柚子汁!
Grapefruit juice! Grapefruit juice!
差不多搞定了.只剩20份了
Okay,we're almost done. Only 20 more to go.
-瑞秋,这些你已校对过? -对,有问题吗?
-Rach,did you proofread these? -Yeah. Why?
没事,他们对你的“垫脑”技巧一定会印象深刻的
Nothing. I'm sure they'll be impressed with your "compuper" skills.
糟了,每一份上面都这样吗?
Oh,my God! Do you think it's on all of them?
没有,我肯定富士施乐复印机弄掉一些了
No,I'm sure the Xerox machine caught a few.
六人行 第1季 第18集 玩扑克
The One With the Poker
他们把这里叫做情侣座. 可是和你对面一点感觉都没有
They call this a love seat but I'm not feeling anything special towards you.
-嗨,小伙子们 -嗨
-Hey,guys. -Hey.
嗨,小姐们
Hi,ladies.
需要什么吗?信件带来了没?
Can I get you anything? Did you bring the mail?
-很多回复 -当然?我们这儿当然有烤饼
-Lots of responses. -Really? Sure,we have scones left!
快念给我听
Read them.
亲爱的格林小姐感谢您的询问,然而…
"Dear Miss Greene: Thank you for your inquiry. However"
-我们有苹果肉桂…-亲爱的格林小姐…好，好，不行.
-We have apple cinnamon -"Dear Ms. Greene...." Yeah,yeah! No.
-怎么了?-你的维萨信用卡账单不少呀
-What? -Your Visa bill is huge!
给我
Give me that.
我真不敢相信 琳达那么好你为何不再和她约会?
Linda's great. Why won't you go out with her?
-我也不知道 -是因为她说了
-I don't know. -ls this about her...
电影《摩登石头族》里的情节真有可能发生?
... "The Flintstones could have really happened" thing?
不只是因为那样 因为我要一个能让我有感觉
It's not just that. I want someone who does something for me...
能让我心跳加速
...who gets my heart pounding.
让我…
Who makes me....
感情经验丰富的女人？
Little playthings with yarn?
什么?
What?
你不是渴望着她吗?
Could you want her more?
谁?
Who?
阿蒂,《发生何事》中 那个尖酸刻薄的女孩
Dee,the sarcastic sister from What's Happening!!.
我早就忘了她了,行吗?
Look,I'm totally over her.
-嗨! -要咖啡吗?
-Hi! -Coffee?
-我们很好 -好的
-No,we're fine. -Okay.
-闭嘴! -我们什么都没说
-Shut up! -We're not saying anything.
-怎么了? -昨晚乔伊哭了
-What? -Joey cried last night.
-谢谢 -我们正在玩扑克牌
-Thank you. -We were playing poker
三点上有巧克力看起来像是八点
There was chocolate on the three. It looked like an eight.
可惜你没看到 他说“准备痛哭流涕吧”
You should have seen him. "Read them and weep!"
结果哭的是他
And then he did.
你们怎么没和我们玩过扑克牌?
Now,how come you guys have never played poker with us?
对,为什么? 好像这是有性别歧视的男人的专利
Yeah,what is that? Like some kind of sexist guy thing?
-这是扑克,只有男人才玩?  -才怪,女生也欢迎加人
-It's poker,so only guys can play? -No. Women can play.
那么为什么…这样的一些,为什么
Then,what is it? Some kind of,like,some kind of,you know
到底为什么?
All right,what is it?
只是刚好女生没加入罢了
There are just no women in our game.
对,我们刚好找不到会玩的女生
We just don't know any women who know how to play poker.
拜托,这个借口真烂 男生都是这种反应
That is a lame excuse. It's a typical guy response.
请问你们谁会玩扑克牌?
Do you know how to play?
不会
No.
-你们可以教我们 -不要
-But you could teach us. -No.
现在开始抽牌
Okay,so now we draw cards.
我不需要换牌对吧? 因为我一把顺
So I wouldn't need any. I have a straight.
-你太棒了! -恭喜了!
-Oh,good for you! -Congratulations!
-菲比,你要几张? -我需要两张
-Pheebs,how many do you want? -I just need two.
黑桃十和梅花六
The 10 of spades and the 6 of clubs.
-不,你不能那样做 -等等,我有你要的黑桃
-No,you can't -I have the 10 of spades! Here.
谢谢!
Thanks!
-不…不能那样 -不…可以,我不需要.我要四张同点
-No,you can't do that. -Don't need them. I'm going for fours.
哦,是吗
Oh,you're
你要四张同点.钱德,你有吗?谢谢,小伙
You're going for fours. Chandler,could you? Thanks,man.
开始吧
Here we go.
我们有鲑鱼乐透和水果盘
We've got salmon roulettes and crudites.
莫妮卡,你在干什么?
What are you doing?
扑克里面,食物的名称不能超过一个音节
In poker,there's no food with more than one syllable.
洋芋片,沙司,椒盐卷…
It's got to be like chips or dip or pretz
我希望你能只卷这一次
I hope you'll let it slide just this once. I was all out of "pretz."
现在开始发牌
Now the dealer
知道了.开始玩真的吧.高赌资,大笔钱
We got it. Let's play for real. High stakes. Big bucks!
你当真?菲比刚丢出两个十一点(杰克) 因为他们好像不开心
You sure? Phoebe just threw away two jacks because they didn't look happy.
我准备好了,发牌
But I'm ready. So just deal.
各位,最后通知!乔伊有
Okay,last-minute lesson! Joey....
三点
Three.
八点
Eight.
八点,三点,好的,不错
Eight. Three. All right,very good.
该死,该死,该死!
Damn it,damn it,damn it!
乔伊有一对5,该你们叫牌
Joey had two fives showing,so for you to raise was
好的?
Yes?
明显而且大胆
Downright gutsy.
-我明白,就是骗 -骗什么?
-I see,so you were lying. -About what?
-骗你们牌有多好 -我在唬你们
-About how good your cards were. -I was bluffing.
什么是唬?
And what is bluffing?
不就是骗的同义字吗?
Is it not another word for lying?
抱歉,我不能再玩了 我在明天工作前得打好履历表
Sorry to break up this party,but I've got to go fax resumes before work.
-瑞秋,我们得算帐(定居) -什么定居?
-We've got to settle. -Settle what?
在维吉尼亚的詹姆斯敦殖民地
The Jamestown colony of Virginia.
乔治三世把它给了我们美国所以…
See,King George is giving us the land....
-瑞秋,是赌局,你欠我们钱 -哦,好
-The game,Rachel. You owe us money. -Right.
你们知道吗?这是她们的第一次 别和她们计较钱了
It's their first time. Let's forget about the money.
不好,我们会付钱的
Hell,no. We'll pay!
莫妮卡,我本来有另一个回复的
Monica,I had another answer all ready.
知道吗?我们要再来一次
And you know what? We want a rematch.
不错,我有钱花了
That's fine with me. Could use some money.
-你很享受这个,是不是 -我想是的
-You're enjoying this,aren't you? -Well,yeah,I am.
这么说你们的组合家具 都是用朋友的钱买来的
So you get your ya-yas by taking money from your friends.
没错,而且我是在“宜家“家具商场买的
Yes,and I get my ya-yas from KEA.
自己得动手装,便宜许多
You have to put them together yourself,but they cost less.
瑞秋,这是扑克牌,玩就是要赢
Look,this is poker. I play to win.
为使我能赚钱别人就得输
For me to win,others have to lose.
如果想和我玩牌就别指望我是个好人
If you're gonna play,don't expect me to be nice.
因为牌一发出
Because once those cards are dealt....
然后呢?
Yeah?
我就不是个好人
I'm not a nice guy.
各位,吃吧
All right,let's eat.
这是从“我爱瑞秋披萨屋”买的吗?
Did you get that from the "I Love Rachel Pizzeria"?
-你们还在取笑我? -别这样嘛,为何学黑道讲话
-You still on that? -What was with that Black Bart speech?
玩起牌来我就不是好人
"When I play poker,I'm not a nice guy."
你扯太远了
You're way off.
我可不这么认为 因为我认为你爱她
No,I don't think so,because I think you love her!
不,或许我曾对她有意思 爱意早已消失
No. I might have had feelings for her at one time. Not anymore.
我只是
I just
马修!你想把光盘怎么样?
Marcel! Where are you going with that disk?
不能再放上去,马修
You are not putting that on again.
如果你按那个按钮,你可真的有大麻烦了
If you press that button,you are in very big trouble.
你知道罗斯那混蛋有多烂吗?
You believe what a jerk Ross was being?
-我懂 -他的好胜心最强了
-Yeah,I know. -He can get really competitive.
什么?
What?
你好水壶,我是莫妮卡,你好黑啊（谚语：罐子笑壶黑，五十步笑百步）
"Hello,kettle? This is Monica. You're black!"
拜托
Please!
我没像罗斯那么烂
I'm not as bad as Ross.
我抗议,画图猜字事件呢?
I beg to differ. The Pictionary incident?
我不是故意的
That wasn't an incident.
我在做手势时盘子不慎滑落
I was gesturing and the plate slipped out of my hand.
-他们叫我去面谈了! -你在开玩笑吧?哪儿?
-I got an interview! -You're kidding! Where?
第五大道萨克斯
Saks Fifth Avenue.
哦,瑞秋
Oh,Rachel!
这就像是母船叫你归队
It's like the mother ship is calling you home.
-是什么工作? -采购助理
-What's the job? -Assistant buyer.
我要用购物…
I would be shopping!
来谋生了
For a living!
是艾莉丝姑姑 她从五岁起便开始玩牌
That's Aunt lris. She's been playing poker since she was 5.
她说的每个字我们都得牢记在心
You've got to listen to every word she says.
-托尼・兰德尔（演员）死了? -我不知道
-ls Tony Randall dead? -I don't think so.
-现在可能已死因为我开车撞到他了 -天啊…真的?
-He may be now. I hit him with my car. -My God,really?
不,唬你们的,第一课
No,that's bluffing. Lesson number one.
告诉你们 玩牌听到的每个字都是狗屁
Let me tell you something. Everything you hear at a poker game is pure crap!
-不错的耳环 -谢…
-Nice earrings. -Thank you.
-坐吧,各位 -艾莉丝姑姑,这位是菲比,她叫瑞秋
-Girls,sit down. -Aunt lris,this is Phoebe and Rachel.
我的车停在计时器前,开始吧
Listen,I'm parked at a meter. Let's do it. Okay?
我们从抽五张牌开始
We'll start with five-card draw.
然后我们开始看牌并且持牌. 我跟南希堂兄说
Then we'll go into the studs and the hold 'ems. I talked to Cousin Nathan.
发牌的时候不要碰牌
Don't touch the cards when somebody is dealing.
南希怎么样?
How is Nathan?
他现在以为他是一个在女人身体里的男人
Now he thinks he's a man in a woman's body.
你是说一个女人在男人的身体里?
Don't you mean a woman in a man's body?
这很简单是吧
It should be so simple.
罗斯,我们能听点别的吗?
Ross,could we please listen to anything else?
好吧
All right.
我今晚可要为此付出代价了
I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
嗨,伙计们,猜猜看?
Hi. Guys,guess what?
第五位牙医妥协了,他们一起推销“Trident”（木糖醇口香糖品牌）?
The fifth dentist caved,and now they're all recommending Trident?
不,是面谈
No,the interview!
简直无法相信!她喜欢我
Unbelievable! She absolutely loved me.
我们谈了两个半小时 我们对服饰的品味一致
We talked for over two hours. We've the same taste in clothes.
我从前还和她的表妹一起去过夏令营
And I went to camp with her cousin.
-这工作简直是太棒了,我可以胜任 -太好了…
-The job is perfect! I can do this. -That's great!
-然后她告诉我最好笑的事 -很好,你讲时我们一定会笑
-Then she told a funny story. -Great,tell us and we'll laugh.
玩牌吧
Let's play poker!
各位听好,我们谈过此事 如果你们不想玩我们完全了解
Listen,we talked about it and if you don't wanna play,it's okay.
对,我们可以玩别的像看图猜字之类的
Yes,we can play some other game. Like Pictionary?
真好笑
Very funny.
-我们想再给扑克牌一次机会 -我想是的
-But we'd like to try poker again. -Yes,I think we should.
-瑞秋,需要我来洗牌吗? -不用了,我想自己试试
-Do you want me to shuffle those? -That's okay,I'm gonna give it a go.
菲比欠7块5,莫妮卡欠10块
So Pheebs owes $7. 50. Monica owes $10.00.
瑞秋,你欠15块!
And Rachel,you owe 15 big ones!
谢谢教我们“斗鸡眼玛丽” 我们该用另一种方式玩了
Thanks for teaching us Cross-Eyed Mary. We gotta play that other way.
这是我的7块5,不过这钱已受到诅咒
All right,here's my $7.50. But this money is cursed.
-什么? -我已对它下咒!
-What? -I cursed it!
花这些钱的人会倒大楣
Now bad things will happen to the spender.
无所谓,我接受.我反正够倒楣的了
I'll take it. Bad things happen to me anyway.
我可以看场电影把它们花掉
This way,I can split them up with a movie.
才刚离开绿色扑克牌机,谁就欠了15块
So that just leaves the big Greene poker machine,who owes 1 5.
你能不能不打劫呢?
Could you be any smugger?
让我看看.瑞秋,我准备开一个画廊
Let's see. Rach,I'm opening up a new art gallery...
我肯定可以用林肯和汉密尔顿的肖像
...and I could sure use the portraits of Lincoln and Hamilton.
男生都这副德行 我是男人我有阴茎
It's so typical. "I'm a man! I have a penis!
我得赢钱增加力量以征服女人
I have to win money to exert my power over women!"
知道吗?还没结束
This isn't over.
我们会再找你们玩 而且我们会赢你们会输
We'll play you again. We'll win. You'll lose.
你们会祈求,我们会大笑
You'll beg. We'll laugh.
我们会赢走你们的每一分钱 你们会永远恨死自己
We'll take every last dime you have. And you'll hate yourselves forever!
我们的意见一致,莫妮卡
Kind of stepped on my point there,Mon.
我无法相信你们输了!有多少?
I can't believe you lost! How much did they take?
差不多30块
Like 30 bucks.
-我会把钱还给你们的 -真的吗?
-I'll give you that money back. -Really?
不,我在唬你!你们还没有学会吗？
No,I'm bluffing! You guys haven't learned crap!
-把牌递给我! -我来行吗?
-Hand me the cards! -Can l?
是的!
Yes!
现在可以交出钱来吗? 如此我们就不必正式玩了
Wanna give us your money now? We can skip the formality of really playing.
不,我倒要看看谁笑到最后,猴子男
No,that's fine. We'll see who has the last laugh,monkey boy.
聊完了没?可以开始玩真的了吗?
Done with chitchat? Ready for serious poker?
你们看,独眼杰克一直看着我
You guys,look! The one-eyed jack follows me wherever I go.
好,玩真的
Right. Serious poker.
-莫妮卡,你还有鲑鱼吗? -你到底是吃东西还是玩牌?
-Mon,got any more of those salmon? -You want to eat or play poker?
-你要上哪儿去? -浴室
-Where are you going? -To the bathroom.
你想上厕所还是玩牌?
Want to go to the bathroom or play poker?
我想上厕所
Go to the bathroom.
-好吧,我去订披萨 -不
-Well,I'm gonna order a pizza. -No!
我仍等着工作的电话通知 他们的店在9点关门那时候再吃吧
I'm waiting to hear from that job. The store closes at 9:00. Eat then.
行,我含薄荷糖提神
That's fine. I'll just have a Tic Tac to hold me over.
未见牌不得下注,下注吧
All right. Cincinnati. No blinds. Everybody,ante.
下…
Yes!
不下
Or no.
-你的钱是我的了,菜鸟 -你的飞机门没关,盖勒
-All right! Your money's mine,Greene. -Your fly's open,Geller.
我刚发现,Joker（11点）就是有个J的poker（扑克）
You know what I just realized? Joker is poker with a "J"!
真巧?
Coincidence?
“巧”（coincidence）就是J碰巧换成了C
That's jo-incidence with a "C"!
-菲比? -我不跟了
-Phoebe? -Yeah,I'm out.
-我跟 -我也跟
-I'm in. -Me too.
我也跟,你拿什么牌?
Me too. What do you got?
你最好逃出浴室 因为我拿五张同花(冲马桶)
You better hop out of the shower,because I got a flush.
好的,好的,好的!
Well,well,well!
回来吧,小子,因为我拿了四张六
Hop back in,bucko,because I got four sixes!
我有四张六!我赢了… 我真的赢了,天哪
I got four sixes! I won! I actually won! Oh,my God!
你们知道吗?我要把小罗斯堆起来
You know what? I'll make a little Ross pile.
看!
Look!
我想这是罗斯的 那个也是罗斯的
I think that one was Ross'. And I think that one was Ross'.
我赚到你的钱,你再无法见到它
Well,I have got your money And you'll never see it
你的飞机门依然没关
And your fly's still open
我骗你低头看了
I made you look
-我跟 -我不能跟
-I'm in. -I couldn't be in-er.
莫妮卡,跟还是不跟?
Monica,in or out?
我讨厌玩牌
I hate this game!
乔伊,你呢?
Joey,your bet.
我像是被满脸伤痕的胖子…
I fold like a hooker who got hit in the stomach...
撞到肚子的妓女
... by a fat guy with sores on his face.
我不跟
I'm out.
-罗斯? -我跟
-Ross? -I'm very in.
-钱德? -不跟
-Chandler? -Couldn't be more out.
我也一样,瑞秋?
Me too. Rachel?
我不但跟而且还要加注 如何?还想再浪费钱吗?
I will see you and I'll raise you. Do you wanna waste another buck?
这一回不会.快嘛,给我看
No,not this time. What did you have?
-我不会说的 -给我看
-I'm not telling. -Show them.
-不 -给我看
-No. -Show them!
-把你的手从那里拿开! -我有同样的约会经验
-Get your hands out of there! -I've had dates like this.
天啊,你真是输不起的家伙
Boy,you really can't stand to lose,can you?
你的脸涨得好红 太阳穴的小血管都浮出来了
Your whole face is getting red. Veins popping out of your temple!
而且衣裤并不相称
Plus,that shirt doesn't really match those pants.
-第一,我没输 -别再谈输了,快发牌吧你输定了
-I'm not losing. -You're definitely losing.
瑞秋格林
Hello. Rachel Greene.
这是有关工作的电话
Excuse me. It's about the job!
芭芭拉,你好吗?
Barbara,hi! How are you?
不,我懂
No,I understand.
不,我没事,快别这么说
Come on. No,I'm fine. Don't be silly. Yeah.
是否还有其他职缺请人?
But if anything else opens up,please
喂?
Hello?
我很遗憾,瑞秋
Sorry,Rach.
工作满街都是
There's gonna be lots of other stuff.
好的
Okay.
玩到哪儿了?
Where were we?
拿五张牌,十一点比较好,大家下注
Five-card draw. Jacks are better. Nothing wild. Everybody,ante.
-瑞秋,别再玩了 -要玩,下注
-Look,Rach,we don't have to do this. -Yes,we do.
-好吧,下注 -下注
-All right. Check. -Check.
-我下5毛钱 -跟跟
-I'm in for 50 cents. -Call.
我跟
I'm in.
我跟你5毛
I see your 50 cents...
而且我要加5块钱
...and I raise you $5.
我以为5毛是上限
I thought it was a 50-cent limit.
我刚失去工作所以想加5块
I just lost a job,I'd like to raise it $5.
各位有问题吗?
Does anyone have a problem with that?
-当然没有 -没有
-Not at all. -No.
输家?
Loser?
-退出 -退出是什么意思?怎么了?
-No,I fold. -What do you mean,you fold?
你不是发牌后就不是好人了吗?
I thought that,"Once the cards are dealt,I'm not a nice guy."
还是只是虚张声势?
Were you just full of it?
我跟
I'm in.
-几张牌? -一张
-How many do you want? -One.
庄家两张
Dealer takes two.
-下多少? -我下2块
-What do you bet? -I bet $2.
我跟你2块
Okay. I see your $2...
再加你
...and I raise you...
20块
... 20.
我跟你20块
I see your $20...
再加到25块
... raise you $25.
跟你25块,莫妮卡,拿我的皮包来
I see your $25 and Monica,get my purse.
瑞秋,里面没钱
Rachel,there's nothing in it.
那就拿你的皮包来
Okay,then get me your purse.
-给你.祝你好运! -谢谢
-Here you go. Good luck! -Thank you.
跟你25块,再加
I saw your $25 and I raise you...
…7块
...seven.
是17块!
teen!
乔伊,我有点不好意思
Joey,I'm a little shy.
没问题,你有什么问题可以问我
That's okay,Ross. You can ask me.
-要多少? -15块
-What do you need? -15.
-这里有10块 -我这里有5块
-Here's 10. -I got 5.
-谢谢 -祝你好运
-Thank you. -Good luck.
再加十七块
I am calling your 1 7.
你拿什么牌?
What do you got?
三张同点加一对
Full house.
败给你了
You got me.
-那确实很难赢 -我以为我们会赢!
-That's tough to beat. -I thought we had it!
没有好牌就是没有好牌
When you don't have the cards,you don't have the cards.
瞧,她多开心
But look how happy she is.
-航空邮件 -飞机.机场,机场75
-Airmail. -Airplane. Airport. Airport '75!
机场77,机场79
Airport '77! Airport '79!
时间到
Time's up!
再见了…小鸟（电影，又名《欢乐今宵》）
Bye Bye Birdie!
那是小鸟?
That's a bird?
那就是小鸟!
That's a bird!
该我了
Okay,it's my turn.
开始
Go!
豆子!豆子!
Bean! Bean!
（与“豆子像得不得了Unbearable Likeness of Bean”谐音）
生命中不能承受之轻（电影，又名《布拉格之恋》）
The Unbearable Lightness of Being!
答对了？
That you get?
这样就能猜中？
That you get?!